Privacy Policy
==============

Our privacy policy explains how we handle the personally identifiable information (PII) that you provide to us when you visit us online to browse, obtain information or conduct a transaction. PII includes information that is personal in nature and which may be used to identify you. CloudQuote uses this website to provide information about products & services. This website includes specific applications which provide more services or enable us to respond to specific questions from website visitors.

What We Collect
---------------

We will collect some personal information about you just because you visit this website. There are applications on this website that provide you with the opportunity to contact us, order services, join our marketplace, ask questions requiring a response, sign up for electronic services, participate in focus groups and customer surveys, or manage your account & payment options. Using these services is voluntary and may require that you provide additional personal information to us. Providing the requested information implies your consent for us to use this data in order to respond to your specific request.

Why We Collect Personal Information
-----------------------------------

We collect PII and other information at our discretion for operation of our marketplace and to sell products and services. The information you provide will be used for that purpose and other purposes. You do not have to give us personal information to visit our website.

How We Use Your Personal Information
------------------------------------

Throughout our website, we will let you know if the information we ask you to provide is voluntary or required. By providing your personal information, you give us consent to use the information for any purpose. We will ask for your consent before using the information if required by federal law.

#### 

* [195 Glenn Way Suite 250  
    San Carlos, CA 94070](https://www.google.com/maps/place/FinancialContent/@37.5141456,-122.2639589,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0xaff3350de005c778?sa=X&ved=2ahUKEwiz45CC79_iAhUZHjQIHZZ2AIIQ_BIwDXoECAgQCA)

#### Learn More

#### FinancialContent

© Copyright 2023 FinancialContent Services, Inc.         [Terms](https://www.cloudquote.io/article/5) | [Privacy](https://www.cloudquote.io/article/6)
